<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="poonlonghei.github.io//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="poonlonghei.github.io//" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2026-01-02T12:04:06+00:00</updated><id>poonlonghei.github.io//feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>A simple, whitespace theme for academics. Based on [*folio](https://github.com/bogoli/-folio) design. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">One Month in Walsingham</title><link href="poonlonghei.github.io//blog/2026/one-month-in-walsingham/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="One Month in Walsingham"/><published>2026-01-02T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2026-01-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>poonlonghei.github.io//blog/2026/one-month-in-walsingham</id><content type="html" xml:base="poonlonghei.github.io//blog/2026/one-month-in-walsingham/"><![CDATA[<p>It has already been a month since I took up my position as Mass and Pilgrimage Office Assistant here at the National Shrine and Basilica of Our Lady of Walsingham. I must confess that I didn’t expect that I would already have been working and living here in Walsingham for a whole month. Truly, time flies!</p> <p>To be honest, I arrived at a very good time, as the main pilgrimage season here at the Walsingham Basilica will begin this coming March. This gives me a few months to learn and become familiar with all the arrangements and management related to the pilgrimages at the Basilica. I can’t wait to see many pilgrims coming here to pray before Our Lady of Walsingham!</p> <p>Once again, I would like to thank all the Fathers (especially the Rector, Fr. Sunday, and Fr. Eric), the Sisters, and all the staff at the Walsingham Basilica for helping and guiding me as I adapt to life and work here at the Basilica!</p> <p>Please continue to pray for my work here at the Walsingham Basilica!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="daily-life"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has already been a month since I took up my position as Mass and Pilgrimage Office Assistant here at the National Shrine and Basilica of Our Lady of Walsingham. I must confess that I didn’t expect that I would already have been working and living here in Walsingham for a whole month. Truly, time flies!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">You are so blessed</title><link href="poonlonghei.github.io//blog/2026/you-are-so-blessed/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="You are so blessed"/><published>2026-01-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2026-01-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>poonlonghei.github.io//blog/2026/you-are-so-blessed</id><content type="html" xml:base="poonlonghei.github.io//blog/2026/you-are-so-blessed/"><![CDATA[<p>If you woke up this morning, with more health than illness, you are more blessed than the million who won’t survive the week.</p> <p>If you have never experienced the danger of the battle, the loneliness of imprisonment, the agony of torture or the pangs of starvation, you are ahead of 20 million people around the world.</p> <p>If you attend a church meeting without fear of harassment, arrest, torture, or death, you are more blessed than almost three billion people in the world.</p> <p>If you have food in your refrigerator, clothes on your back, a roof over your head and a place to sleep, you are richer than 75% of this world.</p> <p>If you have money in the bank, in your wallet, and spare change in a dish someplave, you are among the top 8% of the world’s wealthy.</p> <p>If your parents are still married and alive, you are very rare, especially in Hong Kong.</p> <p>If you hold up your head with a smile on your face and are truly thankful, you are so blessed because the majority can, but most do not.</p> <p>If you can hold someone’s hand, hug them or even touch them on the shoulder, you are blessed because you can offer God’s healing touch.</p> <p>If you can read this message, you are more blessed then over two billion people in the world that cannot read anything at all.</p> <p>You are so blessed in ways you may never even know.</p> <p>A happy and blessed new year of 2026 to you all!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="reflections"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you woke up this morning, with more health than illness, you are more blessed than the million who won’t survive the week.]]></summary></entry></feed>